The Sniffy Octopus
It's like this sure enough.
What's the matter?
Seems someone has been
tracing me recently.
And maybe it's a girl.
How could a girl trace you?
Even you put the earth upside down,
such thing won't happen.
Watch over carefully!
Jaiko
Gian's little sister.
I'm so scared, really scared!
But why did Jaiko trace me?
Really incredible.
It can't be that she likes me?
No...impossible!
That mustn't be like this.
Hello!
Nobita, you're really a happy guy!
Happy? What did you mean?
What? You're pretending! You guy!
What? Jaiko, she...
likes me?
It's normal for you to be surprised.
I'm surprised too.
In fact Jaiko has been unusual recently.
She always suspired alone.
And only ate 5 bowls of rice.
She's my favorite little sister.
So I'm really worried about her.
But I dare not ask her why.
Then when I opened her drawer,
what do you guess I saw?
My picture?
How could it be?!
There's been nothing like
that appearing till now.
It's just a girl's love.
She's the same shy as me.
Even she likes someone,
she dare not tell him.
Once I think of that she's getting
in trouble, I'll feel sorry for her.
So I hope you could ask her for a date
first.
What?
Jaiko
Nobita said that he got something to
talk with you.
So I'll go back to my room
in order to not disturb you.
You should treat her softly. See you.
What do you plan to tell me?
What do I plan to tell you?
It really bothers me too.
I'm very busy.
If you haven't anything, just go home!
Feels relaxed! But it seems
that I've been teased.
Shizuka
Nobita
Shizuka, where are you going?
I'm going to the park to forage feed.
I'm going too.
I'm back to get some feed. Wait for me!
Shizuka...My favorite...
He'!
Gian
Where are you going?
What where to go? Jaiko called me back.
Then you're going home?
Why don't you understand a girl's heart?
She always shows cool to who she likes.
It should be that the boy lays bare to
her. To tell her that you like her.
How could it be?! I don't like her.
You mean that you hate her?
I warn you!
I won't forgive the boy
who makes my sister to cry!
I like her, very much!
You like her so much?!
Look at me as Jaiko,
and say to me 'I like you'!
What?
Hurry!
Jaiko...
You couldn't say it since you didn't
look at me as Jaiko.
Hurry to say 'Jaiko, I like you'!
Once more!
Miss Jaiko, would you like to make friend
with me?
Is it okay?
Say it from your bottom of heart!
I like you...l like you very much.
Then show your attitude.
Come closer! Hold the hands.
I like you very much for sure!
Do you love me?
Of course I love you,
I love you very much.
Really?
Of course.
Doraemon
Doraemon, why could it become
like this?
My future bride should be Shizuka! Right?
Can't be that my fate will be changed?
At beginning you should marry Jaiko
by your fate.
But it'll be changed hardy.
And to change to be original.
I don't want, Doraemon!
I don't want to marry Jaiko.
Help me, I like Shizuka more!
The Sniffy Octopus
To stick down the Octopus' ink will
make Jaiko to hate you.
But its efficacy will be very strong.
It doesn't matter.
Hurry to spray it to me right now.
Doesn't it matter? I'll leave you alone.
Hurry to spray it to me, more!
It's okay!
Then Jaiko will hate me...
You always get me in trouble.
Hurry to go!
Really effective!
Hey, Nobita.
It's on the nose to meet you here.
I got something to tell you.
I made a mistake to think that
Jaiko likes you.
I've asked her carefully.
But it's so funny in the end.
Jaiko wants to become a cartoonist.
But her works didn't be admitted
for many times.
So she's very angry.
Then she wants to draw some funny
cartoon adopting you as a model.
So she traced you and looked at your
picture.
She wants to draw a funny face of you.
Don't know why, I feel very angry
suddenly seeing your face.
It's because Yoo...because of Yoo.
Get off my back!
Idiot! My lover is still Shizuka.
What?!
Shizuka, wait for me!
Shizuka
I hate you! I hate Nobita!
Don't say so, please like me!
Shizuka
He's really a unlucky dog!
With the almighty camp you'll
have a great camping.
To come back from the future which
you haven't been for a long time.
Nobita, I'm back...
Strange, he's not in.
Nobody is in?
Are they in the kitchen?
Nobita, Mom!
It's the Rice Cracker, I'm eating!
For Doraemon, we've went to camp.
How could it be?!
When I come back to the future, the
whole family have went to camp!
Good...
Nothing different without me!
Forget it, let me forgive them!
Didn't they come back yet?
We're home!
Doraemon, I nearly can't stand...
What's wrong?
There's the rubbish everywhere
on the hill.
The empty canisters and paper abandoned
by people were everywhere.
They're very noisy in the other camp.
Adding the noise of the car engine...
we couldn't sleep at night at all!
Just like what I said.
I won't go camping anymore!
What a pity!
Next time I'll take you to have a great
camp!
If it's just camp, that's unnecessary.
I have the almighty camp!
A new invention of the 22nd century.
Really?
I don't want to come back so upset
like this time!
No problem!
Believe me! Let's fly to there
by the bamboo dragonfly.
Because it's a wonderful camp.
Let's call Shizuka to go together with
us.
Okay!
Shizuka
It's Nobita and Doraemon.
We'll go camping.
Shizuka, just go with us!
But...
Just imagine that you've been cheated.
Let's go!
Show a little happy, please!
Look! We can see the valley!
Really!
It's better over there.
So I'll take out my camp.
This one?
Seems like a kennel.
No problem!
So enter to have a look!
Really troublesome!
Just being pulled here by him.
We're now in the camp?
It's early for you to be surprised.
As long as you press these buttons,
it'll become many kinds of rooms.
Let's try!
The floor becomes very soft.
Feels like the carpet.
It comes out from the floor,
and will become a beautiful living room,
right'?
Awesome!
Pressing this button, the wall will
become crystal.
And, pressing this button...
What's wrong...
It'll become the View Flat.
What a beautiful sightseeing!
Having the Bento here must be very
joyful.
I forgot to bring something.
And the drink.
Don't worry, because it's an almighty
camp.
Delivery Kiosk
Just tell me what would you like to
eat'?!
Ramen
Curry rice
Awesome!
You can listen to the music too.
Because of the isolator, no matter how
loud we cry, they can't hear it.
Too great!
I want the fruit juice.
Cola is very cool, not bad!
And also the ice-cream, pudding...
You've ordered too many things!
All of us need pay for that.
Not free?
You can't litter the rubbish everywhere.
Gosh!
You should press this button
at this time.
The rubbish which is picked up will
be sent back to home.
Pressing this button,
it'll become the bedchamber.
Pressing this...
It'll become the bathroom.
Very capacious, feels very comfortable.
YEP!
It's nearly time to play outside.
There're many toys too.
Look!
Really interesting...
It's a lake, let's go over there.
It's so good to come here, right?
Too great!
I got a fish...
Doraemon, what's about you?
Are you ok?
Strange!
What, such a little fish!
Ya...
Great! ...
It became very crowded here.
It's nearly time for us to go back to
our camp.
Is...who didn't turn off the button?
It seems to be collecting all
the rubbish in the mountain.
That's said,
I have something to do in the future.
It's 1:00 dirty!
Doraemon, you can't do that!
You can't get away!
Nobita
Take the Pluto!
What?
Let's take the Pluto to Kyushu.
Yes, really very comfortable!
The bed is very placid.
The light in the street is just like
the arrows passing by the window.
The stars in the sky at night are
very beautiful.
The terminus is Miyazaki of Kyushu.
That means you're at the seaside of
Kyushu.
Swimming here enjoys myself to the full.
So it is, very right!
The seaside of Kyushu is really
beautiful. And very interesting.
Really envy it!
The Pluto!
It's just the new trunk line!
Mom, sleeping at the different places
occasionally should be something happy.
Why should we pay money for sleeping
on the train?
If you want to sleep at another place,
just go to sleep in the ambry.
Well, it's very hot, so I want to
go swimming by the Pluto.
If you want to go swimming,
there's a swimpool nearby.
You needn't go so far specially.
No way! So we have no choice
but to go to the swimpool.
Even Doraemon...
has no idea to get the Pluto out?
Get the Pluto out!
Okay, let's go tonight.
You'll take out the Pluto.
This is a secret for us tonight.
Doraemon, it's been dark!
Okay, let's begin!
What did you stick?
The seal of the trolley.
But how will we get on the Pluto
like this?
You'll know later.
What's that?
It's going!
The trolley game which you're playing is
just for the kids in preschool.
I won't play!
In this case, Doraemon,
you play alone.
I won't play!
The ground is shaking.
It's the earthquake, hurry to run!
Not earthquake, look out of the window!
The house is moving, it'll collapse!
Doraemon, hurry to run!
Hurry to run!
You needn't worry, it doesn't matter.
This house will bring us to
the 4th space world.
So it'll leave the ground.
The 4th space world.
So this shaking is also...
Right!
Just to replace the Pluto by this house.
Will we get to the seaside like this?
Of course.
So just the same with the Pluto?
Drive it to the railway from there.
I'm speeding HP!
It'll running faster than the Starlight!
Awesome...
It's just like sailing on the ocean
under the stars.
This earthquake seems to have lasted
very long.
Yes! Just like that we're on a trolley.
Doraemon
Would you like to go to the dining car?
Yes, I really feel hungry.
Then who come to drive?
Turn it to the auto-d riving.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
I feel I sit in real restaurant car.
The air is good.
But if I tell with someone, they won't
believe.
Because I took room to travel, it's
nice that we needn't carry baggage.
Yes.
What's wrong?
I can't sleep because temblor
I will buy cigarette.
Shops have closed.
But there is self-feeding machine.
When I have smoke this idea,
I can't bear to smoke.
Shit, dad want to get off.
Hurry to stop the tramcar
Hui“!
What a strong temblor
But as if it has stopped.
My house settled down in mount.
Yes.
I'd better not to smoke, I still feel
sleeping.
As if he have slept.
How dangerous.
Nobita, you may go to bed.
When we arrive destination, I will call
you.
Good.
Nobita, wake up.
We have arrived terminal station,
let's go to swim.
It isn't light.
When it is light, we will go.
No, it only can work in night.
We must go home before it is light.
Sea, it is real sea.
This sea bathing is special nice.
But nobody will believe.
Inorganic soporific megaphone
You two gape at all times.
Because we are boring.
Don't you have any funny?
I will go home to watch cartoon.
Hello.
How nice, it is roadster, right?
How nice...
Yes.
My relative brother bought it.
Well, let me take you.
Take us...
I'm pity that I only take two men.
In other words, other one can't take.
Nobita, you said you stay
at home and watch cartoon.
Right, Shizuka?
Yes, he ever said.
It isn't rule
That time is that time.
So... Because...
Goodbye.
Jeez, I go to wall every time..
No cartoon
Oh, mama have thrown it away.
Rest is lettered book.
No picture.
Let me go to watch TV.
Pathetism.
You have transformed a bird now.
Yes, she like a bird.
Cool!
Time is colorful, why is now...
Shit, that guy
I anger.
Why did you anger?
I can't ride roadster and watch cartoon
even TV
Djinnis have given up me.
It isn't serious.
Well, how about it?
Inorganic soporific megaphone
If you use it, even stone
pathetism can work for all.
Why?
Something without life, pathetism
can't work for them.
Because it can hypnotize, it's cool.
Example...
hypnotize mirror
you are TV...
Time is the program played just now
the mirror has been transformed TV.
Turn this knob, you could change channel
Really?
It's funny.
Doraemon, anything will be
hypnotized
Yes, anything.
You are cartoon.
Are cartoon...
It is funny more and more.
You are piano...
You are small trumpet
Good.
You will disturb neighbor.
She is mama, hurry to run away.
Where will we run away?
You are the window of the 1st floor.
What a convenient prop.
Nobita...
Strange, think it over
There aren't piano and trumpet in my
house
That sound just now...
You are handrail...
You are spring-mattress
You are magic rug.
Start...
It's weird.
How come?
What is it?
When did it change?
Help.
Nobita, Doraemon
Hurry to run away.
You are roadster...
Someone will make fun of us if we ride
it.
It is not time to speak it..
Nobita, Doraemon
Nobita, hurry to get on...
Strange.
This two children ran faster.
It's roadster, cool.
How comfortable.
The car's Suneo's
Hey, you are dumpcart.
Strange
How come, why is there music?
Strange, why did you stop here?
Strange, the car stop by itself.
What will you do?
No, it isn't dumpcart.
R... Roadster has...
Magic straw.
Doraemon
My mitt has broken, I want a new.
Take it out.
You are malapert more and more.
You think it is easy if you want to get
you are wrong.
No, I don't think so.
It could be if it has little trouble.
You are malapert. Up to you.
What, it is just normal.
It is magic straw.
If you take it and go around, you
will realize your wish.
Use the magic straw.
Look me
my dream is I could eat Rice Cracker
Rice Cracker is in ambry.
If you eat it by yourself, you will be
criticized
Lend me it.
Good, you have come here, please lend
me straw.
Cool
I want to sneezes, but I couldn't
sneezes, I feel bad.
What?
There is a rule that if you want to
use the straw
you must pay something.
Your mean that I need pay something,
but I haven't anything now.
Well, how about it?
I pick up a glass ball, here you are.
It is different than your thought.
No, if you keep doing it
it will become Rice Cracker one day.
Found it.
It is this.
The button of my suit has lost, I am
finding.
It is good that you found it.
You could eat Rice Cracker in ambry
Look.
How cool, I also want to do...
Here you are.
My wish is mitt
Then, you should go around.
Good bye.
You must have patience to use the straw.
I can't believe.
Someone uses mitt exchange it.
It is that.
Hey, Suneo
Don't joke.
As if it isn't he.
I don't think it has relation with
Shizuka
How about you?
What is syphon? Well...
What do you feel?
It has relation with mitt or others.
I paid 100 yuan buy ice-cream last time.
You should refund me.
Shit, see you tomorrow.
Is it real that it could realize our
wish?
I am upset.
I want chewing
You should let rest of syphon drop out.
Let's play next time.
No...
Here you are.
Thank you very much.
How nice.
Good.
Fly... how nice.
Straw has transformed a candy.
Till it transform mitt, the time is far.
Ah, lummy
Wait... my mitt.
Wait...
Jeez, wait.
You have eaten my mitt.
What's wrong...
It's my fault, but I haven't something
to give you.
Well, this quilt, here you are
I feel that it is difficult that I get
the mitt.
Boy...
Could you come here for a while?
OK.
Excuse me, could you give the paper?
Thanks to you, you help me.
I will deal with a business.
I am thinking it over.
If I am late, I will have a big losing.
Well, I must give you a gift.
What do you want?
Really
Wow...
Good, it's new mitt.
He is a general manager of sporting
goods shop.
That straw realized your wish.
Yes, thanks to the straw.
Nobita, pass the straw to me.
I can't breath, Doraemon take
the straw.
Doraemon...
I only give you one.
Straw, do you hear?
I want a gat model
Do you know, it is a gat model.
It must be a big.
If you said like it, you won't have
any question.
Hurry to go around.
Go there.
You kids
Help.
Stop... Stop.
Hurry to leave.
Nothing.
You wait and see.
Shit, it is skin game.
Ouch.
Good.
He will realize his wish like this.
The signboard marked 'model' defeated
him.
Pom', the model hit his head.
Salvation pill at the eleventh hour.
Thank you.
Please you pick up by yourself.
What? You are transient, you may
pick it up for someone.
You are stingy.
My goods lost.
Someone will care him.
You guy is chill.
Out of my thought, he is so chill,
he goes to far.
I came back.
Nobita, you are this kind of guy.
Strange.
Nobita
You pick up ball for someone, you
needn't waste your one whole day.
Child cried, but you didn't care. He
is wretched.
My schoolwork is more.
I don't know if I could finish, even
it is light.
I haven't enough time to care other.
You are wrong.
Man of the world must help each other.
Salvation pill.
Eat the pill.
Pill, what is impact?
When I find someone has trouble,
I can't bear to help him.
It's good pill.
If all eat
What, you haven't finished your
schoolwork.
How pity. All help him.
I take it all drink.
No, it isn't my idea.
Suneo, your swat is strong today.
It is occasional
Gian, your hualei is strong.
Really?
Hey, Gian
Nobita
I have good pill to give you.
It must not be good.
I think so.
It is this pill.
Really?
If it is good, you eat it.
Gian
What did you do, you have some
complaint, haven't you?
No.
Your trousers is dirty.
Because I have hualei
Let me flap away.
Nobita, you are kind now.
I will do something, although I don't
want.
I must go to other place.
Please take that mitt and batted home.
But.. How come?
I must do my schoolwork, why must I do
this?
I can't bear.
Shizuka
Nobita
That... my schoolwork...
What
No, put it there.
Nobita is strange.
Thank you.
I am sorry.
So good bye.
Thank you.
Do schoolwork...
Mama...
There is a child.
Boy, where do you live? There.
Who know the boy's house or his mama?
Boy, go this way, right?
I think so. I don't know.
It is there.
Who know the boy's mama?
Do you know where dose the child live?
I never meet him.
Someone is finding lost child in the
park.
Thank you.
Hurry.
She is mama.
Boy.
Mama.
I am very worry you.
That brother take me back.
Good, you find your mama.
Thank you very much.
That's all right. So bye bye.
Bye bye.
Bye bye, boy.
Don't joke.
I haven't enough time to do it.
Please help me carry it.
Thank you.
Yes.
So.. Thank you.
Well
Even someone has trouble
I could close my eye and walk
Ouch...
You needn't feel open-eyed
I live alone and have a sick. I feel bad
I know.
I wash cloth and cook for you.
Where is Nobita?
As if the pill couldn't work, but
I haven't time to do schoolwork.
I'm very bad, how about my schoolwork.
Shizuka
I don't know Nobita you are kind.
For schoolwork, I will accompany
you and teach you.
Do you know, don't cry.
Thank you, Shizuka
The magnet
Well, everybody must be careful.
The match will start.
Watch seriously
Cheer up...
Start
Good.
Look me.
It fly to you, Nobita
Ouch...
Nobita, I have told you that you
must clench the ball.
Nobita, you must clench the ball.
Jeez.
After you join, the station likes
this every time.
If you couldn't clench the ball
I will chew out you.
Good.
Hurry to run...
Nobita, what are you doing?
Nobita can't.
Is he serious?
You are ham-handed, we won't accept you.
You go back to sleep.
Why do I play bad always?
What's wrong, Nobita? You look dead alive
It is truth.
You give up because it?
You should try again.
No, I like turning rope game better.
Nobita, you must sport often and
make your body stronger.
But all think I am lumpish.
You could enhance as long as you
practice often.
No, I needn't.
Nobita, he is stubborn.
Well, use it.
Magnet.
If he put it on.
Even he is dislike, he must face
it and take rondure.
He will be able to enhance like this.
Ouch.
Doraemon
What a strange thing.
It is magnet.
If it is rondure, it will be able to
grip it.
Because I don't know what fly
If you don't take it at once,
it will hit you ouch.
I don't want to put it on.
I can't get rip of it.
Shit.
Help.
Please stop... Doraemon
It will be fine.
Ouch...
The whole body has been become round.
Mama, please off with it for me.
It isn't here.
Ouch...
Help...
If he has promoted?
I hope Nobita...
Thank it over, my face and body all
are round.
Take it, Doraemon
You have promoted more than before.
Good.
If only I practice hard, I will be
able to promote.
Yes.
You could take ball easily.
Well, I will go to Gian's side.
Cheer up.
OK.
Good.
I will make Gian them get a frigh
this time.
Left and right are...
Wait
What's wrong?
Jeez.
What? Nobita, you also want to join the
match?
Yes, please accept me.
Nobita, no.
You will fear to take ball again.
Okay.
Only once
But my power is strong, will you be
fine?
I know.
Gian, wait and see.
Really
Yeah...
Start...
Be serious.
Start.
Throw the ball well.
Leave it to me.
Take it, out.
Good, you try to take my ball.
You are cool, Nobita
How do you promote?
Just practice.
Only this, hurry to teach me.
Jeez.
Strange, why did he become strong?
I borrow Doraemon's magnet.
If I put it on my head
I will be able to take all rondure
favorably
Hey, lend me it.
No.
What?
You said that Gian brought magnet.
We must find he.
Hui“!
He has passed through fruits shop.
Help.
Gian is troublesome.
He make many trouble.
How melting.
What's wrong, Nobita? Why haven't you
go home?
Sensei, I have a duck this time.
Oh.
I'm pity that you have a duck
but it is useless that you are worried
for past.
Nobita, do you know why eyes are on the
face.
Because it hope man should be forward...
You don't feel worried for past.
In order to receive tomorrow, you
should lift up your head.
Yes, I know.
Goodbye, sensei.
Why are eyes on the face.
How melting.
Before I haven't forgotten it
I tell someone and affect him.
She is in time.
Shizuka
I want to tell you a good words.
It will affect you.
What is it?
Why are the eyes on the face?
It's simple.
If the eyes are on back of your
head, hair will blot out it.
It is foolish question. Right?
Yes. No, it isn't foolish.
Listen me...
They don't want to listen. You are
boring.
Suneo... why are the eyes on the face?
I will go to cram-school, I haven't
time to listen you.
I want to talk with you before I
gave you text paper.
Why are the eyes on the face?
Because I could use it to watch
my result, give me text paper.
It is bad that you read text paper
and you didn't listen me.
I have a duck again.
I would rather feel worried for past
than I should receive tomorrow.
What did you say, you always have
some clokes.
Stop.
What's wrong?
What did you say?
It is rare
that I could hear a heart-stirring.
But nobody is willing listen.
What? You could tell me.
Listen me...
The eyes are on the face because
it hope that all could be forward.
How about it, if it has affected you.
No.
In either case, nobody listens me.
Wait... don't be self-abandoned.
If you hope that it affect somebody
you could use magic microphone
If you use it to speak, it will
discharge melting sound wave.
It will pass through somebody's
brainwave and affect he.
Really?
What did you say?
I said 'really"?
It's melting words.
I feel melting
You said good, I praise you.
Cool.
I use it and affect all.
But it is cool.
You are a boy.
How could you say snazzy words?
Hurry to tell your dad, he will be happy
Dad.
Nobita he said a snazzy words. It is
effective.
And it affect man.
What did he say?
In either case, it is effective.
What did you say, I don't know.
It is
I will go to play.
Mama, dad
Nobita is good boy.
Yes.
Out of my thought, he could say
this effective words.
I worry him.
Hello.
It could affect dog.
I like the microphone.
I just think aloud. It isn't convenient.
I put it in my pocket.
Gian...
I tell you a melting words.
YOU?
Yes.
Don't joke me.
I bet with my snack.
It's funny.
So, you do it.
You muster more persons
OK, leave it to me.
Let us get together.
Then, Nobita said he will affect all.
And he bet with his snack, all wait to
see.
Hurry to show.
Watch me...
Lost... microphone lost.
Lost...
What's wrong, you can't do it.
So as contract, bring out your snack.
Where did it lost?
Melting child's sound.
Strange.
Could it be...
As my thought, no, it's mine.
Who bully my child? Sorry.
I can't bear.
But this time, I must affect all.
All get together again.
Get out...
How come? You won't be affect?
Nobita...
Doraemon, what's wrong with all?
There is a location shooting.
Rumour said that Xichen Gamei has come
here.
What? That famous swan.
Gamei
How handsome. Look here.
He is grateful.
He will happy because he is grateful.
So Gamei, you sing a song about this
tree.
Okay.
The season, unknowingly, how handsome.
It has disappear.
How excited.
Nobita...
His sound is melting from bottom of my
head.
Gamei sing well.
Be quiet.
Only his sound is nice.
Well.
If I use the magic microphone to sing
now.
Nobita is handsome.
Good.
I couldn't bring it out, where did it?
Cool.
Your sound is lousy.
It is melting.
I am no face.
Nobita, don't run away.
You are my real friend.
Please, let me hear that sound again.
Look, he flower and the grass
Every one
So we walk happily
And sing happily
We are human
Planet in the university
It is the country full of dreams and
smile faces
We walk together
We are human being
Today or tomorrow or the day after
tomorrow
We create together
The city full of dreams